African American Soldiers in World War II Collection
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Digital files
  - Interviews and related material
    - Hartsfield, Arnett, part 5, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_051; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hartsfield, Arnett, part 6, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_052; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hathcock, Cleather, part 1, 1998 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_053; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hathcock, Cleather, part 2, 1998 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_054; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hathcock, Cleather, part 3, 1998 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_055; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hathcock, Cleather, part 4, 1998 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_056; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hickerson, Howard, part 1, 1995 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_057; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hickerson, Howard, part 2, 1995 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_059; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hickerson, Howard, part 3, 1995 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_060; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hickerson, Howard, part 4, 1995 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_061; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Horner, Reuben, part 1, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_063; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Horner, Reuben, part 2, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_064; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Horner, Reuben, part 3, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_065; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Horner, Reuben, part 4, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_066; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hunter, Jehu Callis, part 1, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_067; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hunter, Jehu Callis, part 2, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_068; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hurns, Fred L., part 1, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_069
    - Hurns, Fred L., part 2, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_070
    - Hurns, Fred L., part 3, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_071
    - Hurns, Fred L., part 4, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_072
    - Jackson, Ezell, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_073; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Johnson, Lawrence, part 1, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_074; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Johnson, Lawrence, part 2, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_075; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Johnson, Lawrence, part 3, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_076; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Johnson, Lawrence, part 4, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_077; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Lancaster, Charles, 2010 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_078
    - Lane, Madine Davis, part 1, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_080
    - Lane, Madine Davis, part 2, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_081
    - Lane, Madine Davis, part 3, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_082
    - Lane, Madine Davis, part 4, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_083
    - Madison, Robert P., part 1, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_084; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Madison, Robert P., part 2, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_085; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Marshall, Mick, part 1, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_086
    - Marshall, Mick, part 2, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_087
    - Mathews, John B., 2005 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_088; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - McCullough, William C., part 1, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_089
    - McCullough, William C., part 2, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_090
    - McCullough, William C., part 3, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_091
    - McCullough, William C., part 4, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_093
    - McIver, Dorothy, part 1, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_096; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - McIver, Dorothy, part 2, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_097; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - McIver, I. P., 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_095; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - McKinney, Thomas, part 1, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_098; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - McKinney, Thomas, part 2, 1998 (Container 3)*, mss_86243_145_099; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - McKissock, Cullen, part 1, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_100
    - McKissock, Cullen, part 2, 1998 (Container 3), mss_86243_145_101
    - Montgomery, Harold and Helen, part 1, 1997 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_102
    - Montgomery, Harold and Helen, part 2, 1997 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_103
    - Montgomery, Helen, and Niani Kilkenny (daughter), 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_104
    - Moore, Spencer, part 1, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_110
    - Moore, Spencer, part 2, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_111
    - Moore, Spencer, part 3, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_112
    - Moore, Spencer, part 4, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_113
    - Moore, Spencer, part 5, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_114
    - Moore, Spencer, part 6, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_115
    - Moore, Spencer, part 7, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_116
    - Moore, Spencer and Susie, part 1, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_106
    - Moore, Spencer and Susie, part 2, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_107
    - Moore, Spencer and Susie, part 3, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_108
    - Moore, Spencer and Susie, part 4, 1998, 2010 (Container 4), mss_86243_145_109
    - Payne, William H., part 1, 1995 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_117; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Payne, William H., part 2, 1995 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_118; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Payne, William H., part 1, 1996 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_119; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Payne, William H., part 2, 1996 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_120; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Payne, William H., undated (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_121; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Peery, Nelson, part 1, 1997-1999 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_123; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Peery, Nelson, part 2, 1997-1999 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_124; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Peery, Nelson, part 3, 1997-1999 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_125; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Peery, Nelson, part 4, 1997-1999 (Container 4)*, mss_86243_145_126; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Perry, A. William, part 1, 1997-1999 (Container 5), mss_86243_145_127
    - Perry, A. William, part 2, 1997-1999 (Container 5), mss_86243_145_128
    - Perry, A. William, part 3, 1997-1999 (Container 5), mss_86243_145_129
    - Perry, A. William, part 4, 1997-1999 (Container 5), mss_86243_145_131
    - Perry, A. William, part 5, 1997-1999 (Container 5), mss_86243_145_132
    - Perry, Matthew J., 2010 (Container 5), mss_86243_145_133
    - Pitcher, Alex, part 1, 1998 (Container 5)*, mss_86243_145_136; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Pitcher, Alex, part 2, 1998 (Container 5)*, mss_86243_145_137; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Pitcher, Alex, part 3, 1998 (Container 5)*, mss_86243_145_138; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Pitcher, Alex, part 4, 1998 (Container 5)*, mss_86243_145_139; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Price, Edward, part 1, 1998 (Container 5)*, mss_86243_145_140; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Price, Edward, part 2, 1998 (Container 5)*, mss_86243_145_141; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Stephenson, Joseph L., part 1, 1998, 2010 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_142
    - Stephenson, Joseph L., part 2, 1998, 2010 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_143
    - Stephenson, Joseph L., part 3, 1998, 2010 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_144
    - Stephenson, Joseph L., part 4, 1998, 2010 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_145
    - Stephenson, Joseph L., part 5, 1998, 2010 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_146
    - Stoney, Thomas P., 2009 (Container 6)*, mss_86243_145_147; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Thompson, Allen, part 1, undated (Container 6), mss_86243_145_150
    - Thompson, Allen, part 2, undated (Container 6), mss_86243_145_151
    - Thompson, Allen, part 3, undated (Container 6), mss_86243_145_152
    - Thompson, Allen, part 4, undated (Container 6), mss_86243_145_153
    - Turner, W. E. ("Burg"), part 1, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_154
    - Turner, W. E. ("Burg"), part 2, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_155
    - Turner, W. E. ("Burg"), part 3, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_156
    - Turner, W. E. ("Burg"), part 4, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_157
    - Walton, Woodrow, 1998 (Container 6)*, mss_86243_145_158; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Watt, Fred, part 1, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_159
    - Watt, Fred, part 2, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_160
    - Watt, Fred, part 3, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_161
    - Watt, Fred, part 4, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_162
    - Wesly, Charles, part 1, undated (Container 6)*, mss_86243_145_163; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Wesly, Charles, part 2, undated (Container 6)*, mss_86243_145_164; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Whitley, Edgar, part 1, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_165
    - Whitley, Edgar, part 2, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_166
    - Whitley, Edgar, part 3, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_167
    - Whitted, Clyde, part 1, undated (Container 6)*, mss_86243_145_169; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Whitted, Clyde, part 2, undated (Container 6)*, mss_86243_145_170; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Williams, Henry L. ("Hank"), part 1, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_171
    - Williams, Henry L. ("Hank"), part 2, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_172
    - Williams, Henry L. ("Hank"), part 3, 1998 (Container 6), mss_86243_145_173
    - Williams, Jim, part 1, 1998 (Container 7)*, mss_86243_145_175; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Williams, Jim, part 2, 1998 (Container 7)*, mss_86243_145_176; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Williams, Jim, part 3, 1998 (Container 7)*, mss_86243_145_177; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Williams, Jim, part 4, 1998 (Container 7)*, mss_86243_145_178; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Williams, Jim, part 5, 1998 (Container 7)*, mss_86243_145_179; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
  - Morehouse, Maggi M., personal file
    - Writings
      - A War on Two Fronts: Fighting for Victory at Home and Abroad (exhibit and book) (folder 1 of 6), 2016 (Container 12), mss_86243_145_181
  - Subject file
    - African Americans
      - General history
        - War Stories, Augusta Area Veterans Remember World War II, 2010 (Container 14), mss_86243_145_182
    - Fort Huachuca, Ariz., and the Buffalo Soldiers
      - Photographs (3 of 3) (Container 18), mss_86243_145_184
      - Reunions
        - General, 2010 (Container 18), mss_86243_145_185
      - Video and audio, 2008-2010 (Container 18)
        - Deeds Not Words: The Buffalo Soldiers in World War II, 2010 (Container 18), mss_86243_145_189
        - Inside Buffalo, 2009 (Container 18), mss_86243_145_186
        - Looking Down the Barrel: The Buffalo Soldiers in World War II, 2008 (Container 18), mss_86243_145_191
    - Integration of the armed forces
      - Magazines, newspapers, and other media, 2009 (Container 19)
        - 60th Anniversary of the Integration of the Armed Forces, C-SPAN, 2009 (Container 18), mss_86243_145_192